because you started getting pain once i
restrung the racquet correct
[Music]
we have a new grip huh it doesn't matter
it's an old-school technique and i ever
seen this no the new grip no nothing
nothing gonna happen to the grip on her
don't worry about it i'm just loosening
your strings
i'm taking care of your elbow what were
you asking me is it good to play with a
bandage
i think it's pretty good i don't know
try it yeah yeah they wear some like
they do
yes yes
but i think if we trace back what's
happened when you got this record
restrung that's when your arms started
hurting correct i think so okay so we
loosened the strings a little bit here
anna this is going to feel better
and it's gonna help your tennis elbow a
little bit
good
okay
good anna
good
again come
better
attack it anna go
remember put the racquet to the side a
little bit earlier
when you yeah when you're running up
rack it to the side here
um
go again
good
and i like it
turn
okay turn more on the backhand and wait
hold it
good
be patient on the back end hold it
longer don't open up too early okay
good
good forehand
come on
again open racket face here
good
back inside
attack it anna go
come come come
good try
good
much better
make sure you recover back to the
baseline don't get stuck in the inside
the cord
good up up
and i'll recover back it up
okay come up
and recover back it up
good work
get up there go on a go
hang a try all right eat those low ones
you those low balls you still try to put
some spin okay
go up to the shoulder more up with the
racquet
good work
backhand
and attack it anna go crack it to the
side
okay not bad not bad at all
good
come back in
go again hold it longer hold
on
hold
two things set yourself up better so
you're in a good place
sometimes you're a little too jammed too
tight and also
don't rush it hold longer to accelerate
you got to wait a little bit longer on
your backhand
and then just let it go from there it's
going to be fine
yes
ah a little bit back here it's okay
again
wild
that's the old anna just a wild slap
shot
way out
yeah it's the old slap shot okay we
gotta put some control clean up that
finish a little bit okay
better
okay backhand
again backhand
come on turn more set yourself up
attack
keep attacking on i go
and i'll take it in the air take it in
there
in the air
okay continental grip please on the
overhead continental
and get into the trophy phase trophy
position on the overhead come closer
better do it again same thing trophy
please
beautiful job anna nice overhead very
good
keep your well keep your feet moving
though don't expect the ball to be right
to you keep moving a little bit
okay again
my trophy
you have the racket too far away from
your head keep it a little bit closer in
the trophy face closer to your head
oh okay all right how about this on a
lob run it down
the lob is when it goes over your head
too high you can't do an overhead and
it's back so i have to run back exactly
but
but you know a lot of people do they
attempt to hit an overhead anyway so
they don't judge the height of the law
properly and they try to attempt an
overhead when the overhead is impossible
and then they end up making a mistake
obviously so it's ball recognition you
have to recognize that the lob is too
high for an overhead you won't be able
to reach it and then just not attempt an
overhead just run back let the ball
bounce and do a forehand or backhand
ideally your four hands okay that makes
sense
well it does but like how do you run
back with the trophy position well this
is a great question the first thing you
do is you turn around keep your eye on
the ball if you lose the ball in the air
you're going to get disoriented so you
have to keep your eye on the ball right
it makes sense okay when you run back
you have to run next to the ball not
under the ball let me show you so this
is the most common mistake when people
get lobs and they run underneath the
ball like this on a look and now they
have to go this way
that's all they can do they can do a
shot they can do a shot like this that's
all they have
so what you need to do when you get
lobbed is run next to the ball
ideally you want to leave the ball as
you're running to your left
okay watch this i'm going to get lobbed
watch this next to the ball
and now i can hit a forehand you saw
that
very
easy keep your feet moving
attack it anna como
and avalis come on get in
what about this
anna beautiful job that's how you run
down a lob you see
come on on the run go
control that forehand a little more
and i want a cleaner finish on the
forehand
better not sloppy clean
again
ana it's kind of like a slap shot again
it's very horizontal you're slapping the
ball i like you to control this area a
little more
good
here we go
good anna
again up
attack get in
anna attack get in
hannah what's wrong
here we go on up
and volley
again continental grip please
overhead
good work nice the issue sometimes on
your forehand is that the the sloppiness
is right around the contact and it's
almost like you're you're slapping
someone like this with the hand like
you're hitting and i see the racket
coming through here and you finish very
shallow here on this side
so that's why i keep saying finish clean
make a clean finish like
like we always practice clean finish all
the way to the top here elbow pointing
forward like put more control around the
contact maybe i stopped a control
because i loosen it up so it because
when i squeeze and there's a contact
then it hurts
wow this is kind of like let it i'm
faking it yeah
well
you don't want to do any extremes when
it comes to tennis you don't want to
hold it with a death grip and squeeze it
the racket to death but you also don't
want to be too relaxed somewhere in the
middle hold it naturally a natural
natural hold of the grip here put your
racket put your racket like this let me
do a test put it here
no no i'm going to push on the racket
and put it in front like put some put
some pressure on the rack i'm going to
push on it does that hurt no okay do it
again
does that hurt no no okay what about
what about
this way it hurts okay so so i think
what hold it with my all right so see
here's what happened
i don't think you have tennis elbow i
mean go to the doctor and get it checked
out of course i'm not a medical
professional
you know but i'm telling you what it
makes sense to me what happened
was one of your slap shots overextended
your wrist this way you over flex the
wrist and you pull something here you
want to keep playing with the with the
hurt arm why don't you take just like a
few days off
and ice your arm because it doesn't
sound like tennis elbow to me no
it sounds like a muscular thing
but again this
is a reminder
that even today when we were rallying
there was a tons of forehands where you
you did a sloppy finish yeah so you got
to control the finish you got to make a
clean finish on a clean as clean as
possible maybe don't hit so hard because
i told you when you hit super hard you
really lose control of the arm the arm
kind of does its own thing
so slowing down helps a lot to be able
to control the ball properly yeah
you know what i mean
all right it's time for you it's time
for you to to ice the arm okay
all right
sorry i'm sorry about that
you